{
    "id": "6b6698608bec4fb39e4aec6730a44895",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Peter ..................................... captain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "elected",
                "was elected",
                "has elected"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ................................... opening the parcel.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "was seen",
                "had seen"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His advice .................................... to.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must listen to",
                "must listened to",
                "must be listened to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Will those happy days ever .................................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "forget",
                "forgot",
                "be forgotten"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Who ...................................... this glass?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "broke",
                "broken",
                "was broken"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Grapes ..................................... from thistles.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cannot pluck",
                "cannot be plucked"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Without effort, we ................................. gain nothing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "can be"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Let the weak and the oppressed not ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "insult",
                "insulted",
                "be insulted"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Wealth ....................................... by all and is acquired by some.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is desired",
                "has desired",
                "desired"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We ......................................... the information on our computer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "keep",
                "keeping",
                "were kept"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They ...................................... him admittance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "refused",
                "were refused"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}